Sh-shut up! It was my first time
fighting a monster, okay?!
You're such an idiot.
Stop calling me an idiot.
You came into the forest without even knowing how to fight monsters, so of course you're an idiot.
Why did you come here anyway?
*whimpering*
What, why are you crying
all of a sudden?
Fool.
What?
You can't get stronger because
you're too scared of getting hurt.
My father said there's nothing to gain without sacrifice.
So? Want me to train you?
Who is it you want to knock down a peg?
I'll have you ready to crush them down in a month.
I've been waiting for you.
For me...? Really?
Yeah. That technique you taught me last time was incredible.
Even Hugo was blown away.‎‎ ‎
Wow! Look at you. You're actually starting to scare me now.
So, tell me your name now.
Heh heh. I'm definitely not
‎telling you until you beat me.
Where the hell did you go? I'm strong enough to beat you now...
So why won't you come back?